I following the breadcrumbs yesterday I
did a video on masculinity and
femininity and I also commented on
Charles Eisenstein video when I did it
and I'll link the video on here if you
want to read that but the main point is
that two people had an ensuing
conversation underneath my comment and
reading that this morning I needed
things for me I was like thank you for
this this is if I hadn't written that
comment they wouldn't have had that
conversation and I wouldn't be able to
follow this breadcrumb I realized that
my response to masculinity and
femininity isn't just on that it's
because they're archetypes and I'm
reacting that way to all archetypes
I don't like archetypes because of what
this person also illuminated which is
when you're when you're figuring out
your identity are you creating it or are
you discovering it is it something
outside of you you were living into or
it's something from inside of you that
you're living into those are very
different things
and so if you're if you're creating your
identity a blueprint can be very helpful
and if you're discovering your identity
can be a hindrance so thank you to that
person who wrote that on there and I'm
realizing yes I'm negatively responding
to all archetypes cuz I think they are
holding us back as a society we are
looking for other people to come and and
be the hero because that's what it looks
like a mentor comes and tells the hero
to go on their journey and it's very
obvious here is your quest and that is
not what's gonna happen on this planet
we all need to step into our hero's
journey and the entire universe exists
to be your mentor to be the one to guide
you to leave all of these breadcrumbs
that we do for each other all of these
big huge world events happen so that
each and every one of us can learn what
we're here to learn and that's to
probability and comp like low
probability and complex yet it's
happening it's happening constantly and
there's I don't want people to be
creating an identity I want them to be
discovering identity but I don't get to
decide that I only can decide that I'm
discovering my identity and I do know I
have
labels helpful because they help explain
Who I am to other people and to myself
so when I discovered I was autistic it
made a lot of things collect and put a
lot of things into place all these are
my people and he's that like it but if I
started to act that role if I started to
be like okay how do I be more autistic
how do I look that way more so other
people believe me how do I then that is
I'm starting to create that instead of
discovering that same with when before I
was autistic but I figured out it was
queer and I was there was a very real
need I was like okay well I used to be a
woman who was attracted to men and I
knew what that looks like even if I was
failing and looking like a woman and
being a woman and I knew what male look
like and men and masculine and so it was
okay these two pieces go together
that's easy now that you're queer I'm
like oh god wait am i mask it on my
feminine whom I tracked to and it was
like oh I I get to be I get to be Who I
am and I get to be attracted to Who I am
and it doesn't matter whether they are
vascular if I'm in nowhere that
masculine or feminine
in fact if I'm trying to play a role of
who trying to create something to create
its so that I can attract someone that
is not the same as discovering who I am
as I would love to hear from you in the
comments do you find archetypes helpful
are they blueprints what pieces do you
take from it and I guess that's it they
can be helpful it's an archetype
umbrella as long as you know that that
there's that it's explaining who you are
and you're picking and choosing those
explanations and throwing away what
doesn't work for you versus trying to be
something and that's what I find that
the masculine feminine idea of male and
female and man and woman is that we're
trying to be these archetypes as opposed
to being who we are which partly falls
on the masculine male umbrella and
partly falls under the feminine female
umbrella and that is exactly what I'm
doing in the world is figure following
these bread crumbs fine you know what
the universe is left for me to discover
so that I can discover who I am and be
my best self in the world
my most authentic self in the world not
by society standards by my own standard
how am i living my life and what am I
here to do and that's what I want other
people to do but I can't control anyone
else well hope I can do is put it out
into the world but I'm super grateful I
wrote this comment and got this learning
this morning I'm sure it's probably
talking about no make a group shake
that's what I'll be bringing to it
archetypes alright that helpful alright
everyone else finding them helpful and
I'm just storing the baby over the bath
water because it's quite possible I have
to learn all of my lessons the hard way
I'm so jealous of all of you who do not
anyway welcome to my journey it's
ongoing and I will be back next time
that I find a breadcrumb